export const teamKeys = ['team1', 'team2', 'team3', 'team4'];

export const defaultTeamsData = {
  team1: {name: 'team1', actualScore: 0, dice: null, currentScore: 0},
  team2: {name: 'team2', actualScore: 0, dice: null, currentScore: 0},
  team3: {name: 'team3', actualScore: 0, dice: null, currentScore: 0},
  team4: {name: 'team4', actualScore: 0, dice: null, currentScore: 0},
}

export const Quiz = {
  q1: {question: "Who is the directory of Fidaa Movie", answer: "Sekhar"},
  q2: {question: "Recently released movie of Prabhas", answer: "Saaho"},
  q3: {question: 'singer who sang the song "Vachinde pilla" in the movie FIDA?',answer: "Madhupriya"},
  q4: {question: "Who is know as father of cricket",answer: "Sachin"},
  q5: {question: "movie name in which tammana and venkatesh worked together ",answer: "F2"},
  q6: {question: "what is the jersey number of Messi",answer: "10"},
  q7: {question: "movie name in which Rashi Khanna, Nagarjuna and samantha worked together",answer: "Manam"},
  q8: {question: "movie name in which sonu sood and Anushka worked together",answer: "Arundhati"},
  q9: {question: "name of nagachaitanya in Majili movie",answer: "Poorna"},
  q10: {question: '"undiporaadhey" is the song from which movie',answer: "Hushaaru"},
  q11: {question: "Novak Djokovic a teenis player plays for which country",answer: "Serbia"},
  q12: {question: "Cristiano Ronaldo jersey number",answer: "7"},
  q13: {question: "first Indian women calculator",answer: "Shakuntala Devi"},
  q14: {question: "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 2018?",answer: "France"},
  q15: {question: "Who won the ICC world cup in 2019",answer: "England"},
  q16: {question: "In which year India won the ICC world cup under MSD captaincy",answer: "2011"},
  q17: {question: "Dead Sea is located in between which country",answer: "Jordan and Israel"},
  q18: {question: "who gifted Statue of Liberty to USA",answer: "French"},
  q18: {question: "In Which ocean Bermuda Triangle is located",answer: "Atlantic"},
  q20: {question: "which country is also know as 'Land Of Rising Sun'",answer: "Japan"},
  q21: {question: "In which country white elephant is found",answer: "Thailand"},
  q22: {question: "Which continet has the highest number of countires",answer: "Africa"},
  q23: {question: "which country is largest producer of coffee in the world",answer: "Brazil"},
  q24: {question: "name of first Indian feature film",answer: "Raja Harishchandra"},
  q25: {question: "father of Amitabh bachchan",answer: "Harivansh Rai Bachchan"},
  q26: {question: "Flying sikh of India",answer: "Milkha singh"},
};